greenhousemegastore.com 2017-05-26

# Privacy Statement | Greenhouse Megastore

Effective Date 11/21/13

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To demonstrate our commitment to keeping your privacy protected, our Privacy Policy has been designed to keep you informed about how we collect and use your information.

### The Information We Collect

Certain pages on our website will allow you to order products, submit price quotations, or request to receive information. In these instances, the personal information collected is:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Fax Number

If you are ordering something online to be sent directly to another person (e.g. a gift), the personal information of that person collected is:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Fax Number

Your credit card number may collected in order to process your order. All credit card information is securely encrypted while stored in our PCI DSS complaint order management system and is entirely purged from our database once your order is completed.

### How We Use Your Information

The information you enter into our website is only used to complete your order. This information is not shared with third parties, except for what is required to complete your order (i.e. delivery services).

The information you enter into our website to create a gift card for someone else is only used to complete your order. This information is not shared with third parties, except for what is required to complete your order (i.e. delivery services).

The information you enter into our website when requesting a catalog is only used to send you the requested material. The information is not shared with third parties, except for what is required to send the requested material (i.e. delivery services).

Return email addresses are used only to respond to the email we receive. Your email address is used for no other purpose and is not shared with third parties. Upon purchasing a product, you may choose to subscribe to our promotional emails by checking a box on the website. By default, this field is unchecked, and you will only receive promotional messages if you choose to do so.

To create the best user experience, we use non-identifying aggregate information to make improvements to our website and share with advertisers and analytics trackers. What this means is that we may occasionally tell an advertiser that a certain number of individuals visited _Page X_ on our website, or that _X_ number of individuals have purchased a certain product. No information is given that would allow any individual to be identified.

The personal information you enter online will never be used or shared in any other way not listed above without you first having an opportunity to decline or opt-out of such use.

### Accessing and Correcting Your Information

If you do not have a registered account with us and need to view or make changes to any of your information, you can [contact us](https://www.greenhousemegastore.com/contact_us), and we will be able to make any necessary adjustments to your personal information.

In line with our commitment to your security and privacy, you may be asked a series of questions to verify your identity before the changes to your information is made.

### Social Security Number and Other Personally Identifiable Information Privacy Notice

International Greenhouse Company and its divisions place the utmost importance on protecting the confidentiality of social security numbers, driver's license numbers, credit or debit card numbers, bank account numbers, identification card numbers, passport numbers, alien registration numbers, health insurance identification numbers, and other personally identifiable information that may be collected through the course of business.

Any access to such personally identifiable information is limited to only those employees whose roles require such access. Our employees are prohibited from disclosing or sharing, directly or indirectly, any personally identifiable information unless there is a legal business justification for doing so.

Documents or computer files containing personally identifiable information collected through the course of business will be made unreadable or destroyed prior to their disposal.

### Data Security

Any personal information you enter while purchasing a product or while using our live chat system, such as a credit card number, is encrypted and protected with sophisticated SSL software. For more information on SSL, visit [www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/).

Credit cards are charged immediately upon purchase, and as soon as the charge is placed, the credit card number is deleted from our database. When you receive your order confirmation email, only the last four digits of the credit card number will be appear.

Customer email addresses are not shared with any third parties.

### Avoid Phishing

In the course of email communication, we will never ask you for the following:

  * Social security number or tax identification number
  * Credit card number, credit card security card, PIN number
  * The password you use for International Greenhouse Company and any of its divisions (including Greenhouse Megastore)

If ever you place an order with incorrect information and receive an email from Greenhouse Megastore asking you to correct your shipping, billing, or credit card information, do not respond with the updated information via email. Under the circumstances that this does occur, you can [contact us](https://www.greenhousemegastore.com/contact_us), and we will assist you in safely updating your information.

* * *

### International Greenhouse Company and its divisions are:

  * International Greenhouse Company [http://www.igcusa.com](http://www.igcusa.com/)
  * Greenhouse Megastore [http://www.greenhousemegastore.com](http://www.greenhousemegastore.com/)
  * School Greenhouses [http://www.schoolgreenhouses.com](http://www.schoolgreenhouses.com/)
  * Luxury Greenhouses [http://www.luxurygreenhouses.com](http://www.luxurygreenhouses.com/)
  * Illiana Buildings <http://www.illianabuildings.com/agriculture>

* * *

If you have any questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy of International Greenhouse Company or any of its divisions, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.greenhousemegastore.com/contact_us). 

Send all email requests to: [help@greenhousemegastore.com](mailto:help@greenhousemegastore.com)

OR

You can write to:  
International Greenhouse Company  
Customer Service Department - Privacy Concern  
70 Eastgate Dr.  
Danville, IL 61834  
Phone:  888-281-9337

There are no frequency or fee limits on your ability to review, correct or request this information.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

International Greenhouse Company  
Customer Service Department - Privacy Concern  
70 Eastgate Dr.  
Danville, IL 61834  
Phone:  888-281-9337

OR

Send all email requests to: [help@greenhousemegastore.com](mailto:help@greenhousemegastore.com)
